Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: October 9, 2021

The online version is available at https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

Residence

Bangkok, Thailand

Phone

<u>+66831225471</u>

GitHub

pitchayakit

Email

<u>pitchayakit.p@gmail.com</u>

Laravel	++++	PHP	++++	SCSS	++++	jQuery	++++	Boostrab	++++	Tailwind	++++
								4			
WordPress	++++	Resful	++++	GIT	++++	SQL	++++	С	++++	Alpine	+++
		API								JS	
VueJs	+++	NodeJs	+++	Linux	+++	Python	++				

Over 5 years of software development career in a variety of companies including startup and digital agency. I graduated with a Master's degree in Network Learning Technology, NCU, Taiwan. I has been working on both back-end and front-end website development. Moreover, I am intersted in IoT and Machine learning. Please get in touch

Professional Experience

Lexicon

2020 - prosent

- · Managed up Line CRM system
- Managed up CMS using Laravel
- · Electric search
- Data migration
- · Coaching internships in web development and technical support

Laravel WordPress VueJS Nova Alpine JS

Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- · Managed up to 5 company websites
- Managed up to 2 E-commerce websites
- 1 library website for searching books using Laravel

WordPress Laravel

Empag

2017 - 2018

- · Coaching internships in web development and technical support
- Managed up to 4 web content management systems and tasks at a given time
- · Collaborate with designer in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the designy
- A Support tool for web scraping and export to excel file

WordPress NodeJs

Onestockhome

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017

- Migration content management system to Ruby on Rail platform
- · Developed front-end website using jQuery, Boostrap, HTML and CSS in Ruby on Rail platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improve user interface

Ruby on Rail React

Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML to WordPress and Prestashop
- Managed up to 4 webs content management system and tasks at a given time.
- · Collaborate with project manager to develop website, which is beyond own management project

WordPress JQuery

SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework | HTML Canvas | Joomla | OpenCV

Education

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

Additional Experience

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

IoT Zenbo Machine learning

Smart home with door and light control System.

IoT PHP JQuery